Finding aid for the Hollywood Park records LSC.2254
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Negatives, (1975-1996)
  - Hollywood Park Actions and Club Parties Negatives (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 218)
    A-R.
  - Hollywood Park Actions and Club Parties Negatives (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 219)
    S-Z and Club Parties.
  - Hollywood Park Races and Titles (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 220)
  - Hollywood Park Races and Titles (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 221)
    N-Z and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 222)
    A-L and 3 Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 223)
    M-Z.
  - Hollywood Park Actions and Club Parties Negatives (Summer/Fall) (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 224)
    A-O.
  - Hollywood Park Actions and Club Parties Negatives (Summer/Fall) (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 225)
    Q-Z and Club Parties.
  - Negatives (Black and White) (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 302)
    January-June 1982.
  - Negatives (Black and White) (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 303)
    July-December 1982; January-December, People, and Miscellaneous 1983.
  - Hollywood Park Races Negatives (1 of 3), 1983 (Box 225)
    A.
  - Hollywood Park Races Negatives (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 226)
    B-M.
  - Hollywood Park Races Negatives (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 227)
    O-Z and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Actions and Club Parties Negatives (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 304)
  - Hollywood Park Actions and Club Parties Negatives (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 305)
    Q-Z, Club Parties, and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 228)
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 229)
  - Hollywood Park Racing Negatives (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 230)
    A-L.
  - Hollywood Park Racing Negatives (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 231)
    M-U and W.
  - Hollywood Park Harness Race Negatives (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 232)
  - Hollywood Park Harness Race Negatives (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 233)
  - Negatives (Black and White), 1984-1985 (Box 306)
    January-December, Construction, People, and Advertising 1984; January- December, People, and Advertising 1985.
  - Hollywood Park Publicity Color Negatives (1 of 2), 1984-1988 (Box 234)
    A-K.
  - Hollywood Park Publicity Color Negatives (2 of 2), 1984-1988 (Box 235)
    L-Z.
  - Los Al[amitos] Quarters H.Q.H.R.A. (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 235)
  - Los Al[amitos] Quarters H.Q.H.R.A. (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 236)
  - Los Al[amitos] Quarters H.Q.H.R.A. (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 237)
    T-Z, Titles, and Publicity.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 237)
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 238)
    G-S.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 239)
    T-Z and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 307)
    A-Z and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Action Negatives (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 308)
    Club Parties.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (1 of 3), 1986 (Box 239)
    A-G.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (2 of 3), 1986 (Box 240)
    H-S.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (3 of 3), 1986 (Box 241)
    T-Z, Club Parties and Titles.
  - Los Alamitos Quarters Negatives (Spring) (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 241)
  - Los Alamitos Quarters Negatives (Spring) (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 242)
    D-Z and Titles.
  - Los Al[amitos] Quarters H.Q.H.R.A. Negatives (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 243)
    A-Q.
  - Los Al[amitos] Quarters H.Q.H.R.A. Negatives (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 244)
    R-Z and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Quarters Negatives (1 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 244)
  - Hollywood Park Quarters Negatives (2 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 245)
    D-O.
  - Hollywood Park Quarters Negatives (3 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 246)
    P-Z, Club Parties, and Titles.
  - Los Alamitos Quarter Horse Negatives (Spring) (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 247)
  - Los Alamitos Quarter Horse Negatives (Spring) (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 248)
    M-Z and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (Summer) (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 249)
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (Summer) (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 250)
    L-T.
  - Hollywood Park Race Negatives (Summer) (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 251)
    V-Z, Club Parties, and Titles.
  - Hollywood Park Races, Actions, Titles Negatives (Fall) (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 251)
  - Hollywood Park Races, Actions, Titles Negatives (Fall) (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 252)
    F-Z, Club Parties, and Titles.
  - L.A. Quarters (1 of 2), 1988 May-Sept (Box 253)
  - L.A. Quarters (2 of 2), 1988 May-Sept (Box 254)
    Q-Z and Titles.
  - Negatives (Summer) (1 of 3), 1988 (Box 254)
  - Negatives (Summer) (2 of 3), 1988 (Box 255)
    D-P.
  - Negatives (Summer) (3 of 3), 1988 (Box 256)
  - Negatives (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 258)
  - Los Al[amitos] Quarters (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 257)
  - Los Al[amitos] Quarters (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 258)
    M-T.
  - Negatives (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 259)
    D-N.
  - Negatives (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 260)
    General noteScope and Content
  - Negatives, 1989 (Box 261)
  - Action Negatives (Spring/Summer), 1990 (Box 262)
  - Composite Negatives (Spring/Summer) (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 264)
  - Composite Negatives (Spring/Summer) (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 265)
    P-W and Titles.
  - Action Negatives (Fall), 1990 (Box 263)
  - Composite Negatives (Fall) (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 265)
    A-D.
  - Composite Negatives (Fall) (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 266)
    E-W and Titles.
  - Action Negatives (Spring/Summer) (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 266)
    A-H.
  - Action Negatives (Spring/Summer) (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 267)
    I-Z and Titles.
  - Composite Negatives (Spring/Summer) (1 of 3), 1991 (Box 267)
  - Composite Negatives (Spring/Summer) (2 of 3), 1991 (Box 268)
    C-R.
  - Composite Negatives (Spring/Summer) (3 of 3), 1991 (Box 269)
    S-Z and Titles.
  - Action and Composite Negatives (Fall) (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 269)
    [Actions] A-Z.
  - Action and Composite Negatives (Fall) (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 270)
    [Composite] A-Z and Titles.
  - Negatives (1 of 3), 1991-1993 (Box 292)
    April, May, June, July, November, December 1993.
  - Negatives (2 of 3), 1991-1993 (Box 293)
    April, May, June, July, November, December 1992; November and December 1993.
  - Negatives (3 of 3), 1991-1993 (Box 294)
    April, May, June, July, November, December 1991.
  - Action Negatives (Spring) (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 271)
  - Action Negatives (Spring) (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 272)
    S-Z.
  - Composite Negatives (Spring) (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 272)
    A-J.
  - Composite Negatives (Spring) (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 273)
    K-Z and Titles.
  - Races and Action (Fall) (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 274)
    [Races] A-Z.
  - Races and Action (Fall) (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 275)
    [Action] A-Z.
  - Composite (Spring) (1 of 3), 1993 (Box 275)
  - Composite (Spring) (2 of 3), 1993 (Box 276)
    D-Q.
  - Composite (Spring) (3 of 3), 1993 (Box 277)
    S-Z, Titles.
  - Actions (Spring) (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 277)
  - Actions (Spring) (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 278)
    F-Z, Titles.
  - Composites Action (Fall) (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 279)
    [Composites] A-Z and Titles; [Actions] A-L.
  - Composites Action (Fall) (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 280)
    [Actions] M-Z and Titles.
  - Actions (Summer) (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 280)
  - Actions (Summer) (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 281)
    L-Z, Titles.
  - Groups (Summer) (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 281)
    With May, June, and July; some envelopes are annotated with what appear to be group names.
  - Groups (Summer) (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 282)
    With May, June, July, November, December. Some are annotated with what appear to be group names.
  - Composites (Summer) (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 283)
  - Composites (Summer) (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 284)
    O-Z, Titles.
  - Actions and Composites (Fall) (1 of 3), 1994 (Box 284)
    [Actions] A-L.
  - Actions and Composites (Fall) (2 of 3), 1994 (Box 285)
    [Actions] M-Z, Titles, and Unsorted. [Composites] A-O.
  - Actions and Composites (Fall) (3 of 3), 1994 (Box 286)
    [Composites] P-Z, Titles and unsorted.
  - Composites (Summer) (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 286)
    A-I.
  - Composites (Summer) (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 287)
    J-Z and Titles.
  - Composites (Summer) (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 288)
  - Actions (Summer) (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 288)
  - Actions (Summer) (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 289)
  - Groups (Summer/Fall 1995, Summer 1996) (1 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 289)
    Summer/Fall 1995.
  - Groups (Summer/Fall 1995, Summer 1996) (2 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 290)
    Summer/Fall 1995 and Summer 1996.
  - Groups (Summer/Fall 1995, Summer 1996) (3 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 291)
    Summer 1996.
- Press Clippings, December 1982-2003
  The series is arranged in a loose chronological order.
  Original and photocopied press clippings, most annotated with the publication date. Included are pieces about Hollywood Park, Santa Anita, and Los Alamitos racetracks, horses and horse racing. Among the various newspapers represented are the Daily Racing Forum, the Los Angeles Times, the Herald Examiner, the Racing Times, and the Thoroughbred Times. Beginning in 1995 the files were titled by the topics of 'horse races' or 'stadiums, arenas, and casinos.
  - Newspaper clippings, 1982 Dec - 1984 June (Box 129)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1984 June - Dec (Box 130)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985 Jan - May (Box 131)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985 June - Oct (Box 132)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1985 Oct - 1988 Mar 12 (Box 133)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1988 Mar 11 - Dec (Box 134)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1989 Feb - Dec (Box 135)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1990 Jan - May (Box 136)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1990 May - Aug (Box 137)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1990 Aug - Nov (Box 138)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1990 Nov - 1991 Apr (Box 139)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1991 Mar - July (Box 140)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1991 Aug - Dec, 1993 Jan - Feb (Box 141)
  - Hollywood Park News Release, 1993 Jan - May (Box 142)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1993 Mar - Dec, 1994 Feb - Mar (Box 142)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1994 Mar - Oct (Box 143)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1994 June - Dec (Box 144)
  - Horse Racing, 1994 Nov - 1995 June (Box 145)
  - Stadiums, Arenas, and Casinos, 1994 Dec (Box 145)
  - Stadiums, Arenas, and Casinos, 1995 July, Nov - Dec (Box 146)
  - Horse Racing, 1995 July - 1996 Mar (Box 146)
  - Stadiums, Arenas, and Casinos, 1996 Feb - Sept (Box 147)
  - Horse Racing, 1996 April - Sept (Box 147)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1996 Oct - 1997 July (Box 148)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1997 Aug - 2003 Nov, and undated (Box 149)
- Chart books, Bulk, 1980-1997 (September-October 1945; 1977-1978; 1980-1997); 1980-1997
  The Chart Books are arranged alphabetically by race track.
  The Chart Book series are scrapbook-like volumes that contain clippings of race charts from what appear to be newspaper publications. Race tracks represented include the Oak Tree, Golden Gate, Santa Anita, Bay Meadows, and Los Alamitos; there is only one volume specifically representing Hollywood Park. The charts consists of statistics regarding specific horses and races, jockeys, and odds.
  - Bay Meadows, Golden Gate Fields, 1981 (Box 151)
  - Bay Meadows, 1985-1986 (Box 157)
  - Bay Meadows, 1986 - 1987 (Box 16)
  - Bay Meadows, 1987-1988 (Box 159)
  - Bay Meadows, 1988 Aug 24 - 1989 Jan 7 (Box 161)
  - Bay Meadows Continued, 1989 Jan 7 - Jan 22 (Box 161)
  - Bay Meadows Continued, 1989-1990 (Box 164)
  - Bay Meadows, 1990 (Box 165)
  - Bay Meadows Continued, 1990-1991 (Box 167)
  - Bay Meadows, 1991 (Box 169)
  - Bay Meadows Continued, 1991-1992 (Box 170)
  - Del Mar, Del Mar Fair, Oak Tree Racing (Santa Anita), 1981 July 22 - Sept 9; 1981 Sept 10 - Sept 18; 1981 Sept 30 - Nov 9 (Box 152)
  - Del Mar, Oak Tree Meeting (At Santa Anita), 1982 Jul 21 - Sept 8; 1982 June 29 - Nov 1 (Box 153)
  - Del Mar (Meeting), Oak Tree Meeting (At Santa Anita), 1983 July 27 - Sept 14; 1983 Oct 5 - Nov 14 (Box 154)
  - Del Mar Meeting, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Del Mar, 1985 (Box 156)
  - Del Mar and Pomona, 1986 (Box 158)
  - Del Mar, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Del Mar, 1988 (Box 158)
  - Del Mar, 1989 (Box 162)
  - Del Mar, 1990 (Box 166)
  - Del Mar, 1991 (Box 168)
  - Del Mar, 1992 (Box 172)
  - Del Mar Racing Club, 1993 Summer (Box 172)
  - Del Mar, 1994 (Box 174)
  - Del Mar, Fairplex, 1995 (Box 175)
  - Del Mar, Fairplex, 1996 (Box 177)
  - Fairplex Park (Pomona), 1989 (Box 164)
  - Fairplex Park, 1990 (Box 167)
  - Fairplex Park, 1992-1994 (Box 173)
  - Golden Gate, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Golden Gate, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Golden Gate Field, 1988 (Box 160)
  - Golden Gate Fields, 1989 (Box 163)
  - Golden Gate Fields Continued, 1989 (Box 164)
  - Golden Gate Fields, 1990 (Box 166)
  - Golden Gate Fields Continued, 1990 (Box 166)
  - Golden Gate Fields, 1991 (Box 169)
  - Hollywood Park, 1945 Sept 5 - Oct 20 (Box 24)
  - Oak Tree, 1984 (Box 155)
  - Oak Tree, 1985 (Box 156)
  - Oak Tree, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Oak Tree, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Oak Tree, 1988 (Box 160)
  - Oak Tree, 1989 (Box 163)
  - Oak Tree, 1990 (Box 167)
  - Oak Tree, 1991 (Box 170)
  - Oak Tree, 1992 (Box 170)
  - Oak Tree, 1993 (Box 172)
  - Oak Tree, 1994 (Box 174)
  - Oak Tree, 1995 (Box 175)
  - Oak Tree, 1996 (Box 176)
  - Pomona, Santa Anita, Oak Tree Meeting, Los Alamitos, 1980 (Box 150)
  - Santa Anita, 1977 - 1978 (Box 14)
  - Santa Anita, 1981 (Box 150)
  - Santa Anita, 1981 (Box 151)
  - Santa Anita Park (86 Days), 1981 Dec 26 - 1982 April 21 (Box 152)
  - Santa Anita Park (89 Racing Days), 1982 Dec 26 - 1983 April 25 (Box 153)
  - [Santa Anita], 1983-1984 (Box 154)
  - Santa Anita, 1984-1985 (Box 155)
  - Santa Anita (Winter Meet), 1985-1986 (Box 157)
  - Santa Anita, 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Santa Anita, 1987-1988 (Box 159)
  - Santa Anita, 1988-1989 (Box 162)
  - Santa Anita, 1989-1990 (Box 165)
  - Santa Anita, 1990-1991 (Box 168)
  - Santa Anita, 1991-1992 (Box 171)
  - Santa Anita (Winter/Spring), 1992-1993 (Box 171)
  - Santa Anita, 1993-1994 (Box 173)
  - Santa Anita, 1994-1995 (Box 174)
  - Santa Anita, 1995-1996 (Box 176)
  - Santa Anita, 1996-1997 (Box 177)
- Serials (Box 335, Box 336, Box 337, Box 338, Box 339, Box 340, Box 341, Box 342, Box 343, Box 344, Box 345, Box 346, Box 347, Box 348, Box 349, Box 350, Box 351, Box 352, Box 353, Box 354, Box 355, Box 356, Box 357, Box 358, Box 359, Box 360, Box 361, Box 362, Box 363, Box 364, Box 365, Box 366, Box 367, Box 368, Box 369, Box 370, Box 371, Box 372, Box 373, Box 374, Box 375, Box 376, Box 377, Box 378, Box 379, Box 380, Box 381, Box 382, Box 383, Box 384, Box 385, Box 386, Box 387, Box 388, Box 389, Box 390, Box 391, Box 392, Box 393, Box 394, Box 395, Box 396, Box 397, Box 398, Box 399, Box 400, Box 401, Box 402, Box 403, Box 404, Box 405, Box 406, Box 407, Box 408, Box 409, Box 410, Box 411, Box 412, Box 413, Box 414, Box 415, Box 416, Box 417, Box 418, Box 419, Box 420, Box 421, Box 422, Box 423, Box 424, Box 425, Box 426, Box 427, Box 428, Box 429, Box 430, Box 431, Box 432, Box 433, Box 434, Box 435, Box 436, Box 437, Box 438, Box 439, Box 440, Box 441, Box 442, Box 443, Box 444, Box 445, Box 446, Box 447, Box 448, Box 449, Box 450, Box 451, Box 452, Box 453, Box 454, Box 455, Box 456, Box 457, Box 458, Box 459, Box 460, Box 461, Box 462, Box 463, Box 464, Box 465, Box 466, Box 467, Box 468, Box 469, Box 470, Box 471, Box 472, Box 473, Box 474, Box 475, Box 476, Box 477, Box 478, Box 479, Box 480, Box 481, Box 482, Box 483, Box 484, Box 485, Box 486, Box 487, Box 488, Box 489, Box 490, Box 491, Box 492, Box 493, Box 494, Box 495, Box 496, Box 497, Box 498, Box 499, Box 500, Box 501, Box 502)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Serials may be accessed, but they are currently undescribed.